GOOD, YOU GUYS ARE ALL HERE.
HEY, WHAT'S UP?
WELL, I HAVE A JOB INTERVIEW
AT RALPH LAUREN TOMORROW.
Ross:
OH...
CONGRATULATIONS.
OH, BOY, THAT GUY'S
UNDERWEAR SUCKS.
WHAT?
OH, I GOT THIS PAIR MARKED "XS."
LET ME TELL YOU, THERE WAS NO
ROOM FOR "XS" ANYTHING IN THERE.
Rachel:
ANYWAY
I'LL BE THE COORDINATOR
OF THE WOMEN'S COLLECTION.
I'LL WORK
RIGHT UNDER THE DIRECTOR.
IT'S THE PERFECT
PERFECT JOB FOR ME.
WELL, IF YOU NAIL THE INTERVIEW,
YOU'LL GET IT.
YOU WANT TO WORK
ON YOUR INTERVIEW SKILLS?
OKAY.
ALL RIGHT.
HI.
VERY GOOD HANDSHAKE.
GOOD WRIST ACTION.
LET ME TRY.
OKAY.
OH, MY GOD!
WHAT DID I EVER DO TO YOU?
DID I SQUEEZE
IT TOO HARD?
LET'S JUST SAY
I'M GLAD I'M NOT CHANDLER.
♪ SO NO ONE TOLD YOU
LIFE WAS GONNA BE THIS WAY ♪
♪ YOUR JOB'S A JOKE,
YOU'RE BROKE ♪
♪ YOUR LOVE LIFE'S D.O.A. ♪
♪ IT'S LIKE YOU'RE ALWAYS
STUCK IN SECOND GEAR ♪
♪ WHEN IT HASN'T BEEN
YOUR DAY, YOUR WEEK ♪
♪ YOUR MONTH,
OR EVEN YOUR YEAR ♪
♪ BUT I'LL BE THERE FOR YOU ♪
♪ WHEN THE RAIN STARTS TO POUR ♪
♪ I'LL BE THERE FOR YOU ♪
♪ LIKE I'VE BEEN THERE BEFORE ♪
♪ 'CAUSE YOU'RE THERE
FOR ME, TOO. ♪
THAT'S RIGHT, ROSS-- I CAN
SEE YOU IN YOUR NEW APARTMENT
AND YOU CAN SEE ME--
SAME AS YESTERDAY.
SAME AS THE DAY BEFORE.
IS HE DOING
HIS "SHARK ATTACK" BIT YET?
NOPE. WAIT.
THERE HE GOES.
VERY FUNNY, ROSS.
VERY LIFELIKE AND FUNNY. OKAY.
OH, NO, NO, NO.
I WASN'T WAVING AT YOU, LADY.
WHOA, MAYBE I WAS.
HEY, MONICA, THIS TOTALLY HOT
GIRL IN ROSS' BUILDING
IS FLIRTING WITH ME.
GET IN THERE, MAN.
FLIRT BACK. MIX IT UP.
YEAH, I'M DOWN WITH THAT.
OKAY, HERE GOES.
HOW... YOU...
A-DOING?!
IT WORKED.
SHE'S WAVING ME OVER.
OKAY, I'LL BE RIGHT OVER.
LET'S SEE.
SHE'S ON THE THIRD FLOOR.
WOW, SHE IS PRETTY, HUH?
TELL ME ABOUT IT, HUH?
NO, NO, NO.
NO, NO, I'M NOT WITH HER.
NO, THAT'S JUST MONICA.
BLEAH! UH-UH.
HEY, JOEY.
GREAT STUFF, HUH?
THIS YOUR PLACE?
YEAH, OF COURSE, IT IS.
COME ON IN.
WOO, WOO
GO BY THE WINDOW.
YOU CAN PRETEND TO BE SURFING.
BUT I COUNTED.
YOU'RE NOT SUPPOSED
TO LIVE HERE.
OH, MAN.
( grunts )
WHAT HAPPENED?
I ENDED UP
AT ROSS' PLACE.
I MUST HAVE MISCOUNTED
OR SOMETHING.
DAMN! SHE'S NOT
THERE ANYMORE.
LOOK, ROSS IS DOING HIS
"WATCHING TV" BIT.
NO, JOEY, I THINK
HE'S JUST WATCHING TV.
Man:
We've lost visual contact
with the suspect.
OKAY, NOW I REALLY
HAVE TO GO.
IT'S SO UNFAIR
THAT OUR DATE
HAS TO GET CUT SHORT
JUST 'CAUSE SOME GUY
SHOT AT A STORE CLERK.
I KNOW, BUT IT'S
MY JOB, SWEETHEART.
OKAY, BUT MAYBE
I COULD COME, TOO.
Suspect has just emerged naked
from the sewer.
ALL RIGHT, YOU GO.
OKAY, BYE.
OH, GOD.
WHAT?
OH, I JUST MISS HIM SO MUCH.
WOW, FOR JUST A WEEK
YOU GUYS ARE
REALLY CLOSE, HUH?
YEAH, IT'S WEIRD.
I CAN'T HELP IT, THOUGH.
HE'S SO SWEET.
HE'S LIKE THIS
LITTLE PUPPY DOG, YOU KNOW?
BUT LIKE A REALLY TOUGH ONE
WHO SHOOTS BAD GUYS.
I JUST LOVE
THE BEGINNING PARTS
OF RELATIONSHIPS,
YOU KNOW?
YOU JUST CAN'T KEEP
YOUR HANDS OFF EACH OTHER.
I KNOW. IT IS THE BEST.
OH, GOD.
SO HOW LONG DID THAT LAST
FOR YOU AND CHANDLER?
WHAT? IT'S STILL GOING ON.
COME ON.
SERIOUSLY, WHEN DID IT END?
I AM SERIOUS.
I MEAN, WE'RE ALL OVER
EACH OTHER ALL THE TIME.
WELL, YOU KNOW
WHERE YOU ARE
BETTER THAN I DO.
I WAS JUST CURIOUS.
WHY DON'T YOU JUST CALM DOWN,
PHOEBE, ALL RIGHT?!
WHY DON'T YOU
JUST GET
ALL YOUR FACTS
BEFORE YOU RUN AROUND
TELLING EVERYBODY
YOU'RE THE ONLY HOT COUPLE?
GOD, I AWOKE THE BEAST.
I WAS WRONG
OBVIOUSLY.
I JUST, I MISSPOKE.
IT'S OKAY.
WELL, IT IS OKAY.
I MEAN, AS LONG
AS YOU KNOW THAT
CHANDLER AND I ARE
ALSO VERY HOT AND FIERY.
I MEAN, JUST
AS HOT AS YOU.
I MEAN, OUR FLAME...
WHOO!
IT IS ON FIRE!
HEY, MONICA,
HERE'S YOUR BROOM BACK.
MMM.
YOU ARE SO CUTE.
OH, HEY.
HOW'D THE INTERVIEW GO?
OH, HORRIBLE.
I DID THE STUPIDEST,
MOST EMBARRASSING THING.
DID YOU TELL THE GUY
YOU WANTED TO HAVE SEX
WITH HIS WIFE
AND THEN FALL
RIGHT OUT OF
YOUR CHAIR?
NO.
SO WHAT HAPPENED?
OH, IT WAS HORRIBLE.
AND THE INTERVIEW PART
WENT SO WELL.
I EVEN MADE HIM LAUGH.
HE SAID SOMETHING ABOUT A BOAT
AND I WAS, LIKE, WELL
"YEAH, IF YOU'VE GOT
ENOUGH LIFE JACKETS."
OH. TRUST ME.
IT-IT WAS ACTUALLY...
IT WAS VERY FUNNY.
ANYWAY, SO
WE WERE SAYING GOOD-BYE
AND, UH, OH...
WHAT HAPPENED?
ALL RIGHT, WELL,
WE WERE SHAKING HANDS
AND HE KIND OF LEANED
IN TOWARD ME...
YOU KNOW, MAYBE
HE WAS GOING TO OPEN THE DOOR
BUT I TOTALLY MISREAD HIM
AND, I, UH...
YOU KNOW?
YOU KISSED HIM?
I DIDN'T KNOW WHAT ELSE TO DO.
WELL, YOU COULD'VE TRIED...
NOT KISSING HIM.
THANKS, CHANDLER.
HEY, RACH, A GUY
FROM RALPH LAUREN CALLED.
YOU GOT A SECOND INTERVIEW.
I CAN'T BELIEVE IT.
I GOT A SECOND INTERVIEW.
YES.
I BET THAT KISS
ISN'T LOOKING
LIKE SUCH A MISTAKE
NOW, IS IT?
WAIT. YOU DON'T THINK
THAT'S WHY HE WANTS ME BACK?
YEAH.
NO?
KISS? WHAT ARE YOU
TALKING ABOUT?
OH, WELL, I-I ACCIDENTALLY
KISSED HIM IN THE INTERVIEW
AND NOW HE WANTS ME BACK.
YOU KNOW, OF COURSE, BECAUSE
"LET'S BRING BACK THE GIRL
WHO KISSES EVERYBODY."
COME ON, RACH.
OH, MY GOD, WHAT IF HE THINKS
I'M THE KIND OF GIRL
THAT WILL JUST SLEEP WITH HIM?
HE PROBABLY WANTS
YOU BACK
BECAUSE YOU'RE RIGHT
FOR THE JOB.
MAYBE. I-I...
I DON'T KNOW.
OH, GOD! HOW COULD
I BE SO STUPID?!
OH, RACHEL, LOOK,
DON'T SAY THAT.
I-I THINK YOU
JUST NEED A HUG FROM JOEY.
COME ON.
SHE'S BACK!
HOT GIRL'S BACK!
AH, WELL, I'M NOT
TOTALLY BACK YET
BUT I REALLY
APPRECIATE YOUR...
NO, IN ROSS' BUILDING,
SHE'S BACK!
OKAY. WAIT THERE.
I'LL BE OVER IN A SECOND.
ONE, TWO, THREE, FOUR.
GOT IT!
I GOT TO CHECK OUT
THIS HOT GIRL.
THERE SHE IS.
DAMN IT!
DID YOU MOVE?!
YES.
I LIVED WITH YOU GUYS
FOR A WHILE
AND THEN I FOUND
THIS PLACE.
I'M ROSS.
( door closes )
YES?
UH...
DO YOU HAPPEN TO HAVE
A HOT GIRL IN THERE?
NOPE.
I'M ALL ALONE.
YEAH. SORRY ABOUT THAT.
OH. HEY, LITTLE GIRL.
UH, IS YOUR MOMMY OR SISTER
OR BABY-SITTER
BY ANY CHANCE A HOT GIRL?
DADDY!
LATER, GIRL.
OH, MAN.
HOT GIRL?!
HI, RACHEL.
HI.
COME ON IN.
OKAY.
IT'S REALLY NICE
TO SEE YOU AGAIN.
THANK YOU.
OH, RACHEL
UH...
WHAT?
JUST, UH...
EXCUSE ME?
YEAH, LET ME...
WAIT! WAIT!
ALL RIGHT.
I SEE WHAT'S GOING ON HERE.
LOOK, I AM SORRY
IF I HAVE GIVEN YOU
THE WRONG IMPRESSION
BUT I AM NOT SOME HUSSY
WHO WILL JUST SLEEP AROUND
TO GET AHEAD.
WELL...
EVEN THOUGH
I KISSED YOU
THAT DOES
NOT GIVE YOU
THE RIGHT TO DEMAND SEX FROM ME.
I DO NOT WANT THIS JOB THAT BAD.
GOOD DAY, SIR.
OH!
YOU ARE NOT GOING
TO BELIEVE
WHAT THAT SLEAZEBALL
FROM RALPH LAUREN DID TO ME.
( all mumbling )
OKAY. OKAY, THAT'S AMAZING.
HOW DID YOU KNOW THAT?
YOU GOT INK ON YOUR LIP.
OH.
OH...
WHAT DO YOU SAY
MAYBE SOME TIME,
I HOLD YOUR GUN?
I DON'T KNOW.
WE'RE REALLY NOT
SUPPOSED TO DO THAT.
WHAT COULD HAPPEN?
I MEAN...
YEAH. I'M GOING TO SAY NO.
PHOEBE, DO YOU WANT
TO GO SEE A MOVIE
AFTER DINNER TONIGHT?
OH, WE CAN'T.
WE ALREADY HAVE PLANS.
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
UM, WELL, SAME THING
WE DID ALL DAY.
JUST HANG OUT AT
GARY'S APARTMENT.
HE IS SO AMAZING.
WE NEVER LEFT THE BEDROOM.
BUT HAVE FUN
AT THE MOVIE.
OH, WELL, WE'RE
NOT SEEING A MOVIE.
YOU'RE NOT?
THEN WHY DID YOU ASK US
IF WE WANTED TO GO?
OH, UM, THAT'S BECAUSE
I JUST, YOU KNOW...
WANTED TO KNOW WHAT
YOU GUYS WERE DOING
SO, YOU KNOW
YOU WOULDN'T
WALK IN ON ME
AND CHANDLER
WHILE WE WERE...
YOU KNOW, DOING
IT ALL NIGHT.
WILL YOU EXCUSE ME
FOR JUST A SECOND?
OKAY.
( clears throat )
CHANDLER,
CAN I SEE YOU FOR A SECOND?
UH, YEAH.
OKAY.
WE HAVE GOT
TO BEAT THEM.
WHAT?
BECAUSE...
GARY AND PHOEBE
THINK THEY'RE A HOTTER
COUPLE THAN WE ARE.
OH. SO?
"SO"?
SO WE'VE GOT
TO GO UPSTAIRS
AND HAVE A LOT OF SEX
AND PROVE THEM WRONG.
YOU HAVE GOT TO STOP
THIS COMPETITIVE THING.
OKAY? IT'S CRAZY.
JUST TO IMPRESS
GARY AND PHOEBE
YOU WANT ME TO GO UPSTAIRS
AND HAVE SEX WITH YOU
OVER AND OVER AND OVER...
AND I'M SAYING
NO TO THIS WHY?
GET YOUR COAT!
HI.
EXCUSE ME.
YOU SHOULD
CHECK THIS OUT.
TELL THE OTHER TENANTS.
APPARENTLY,
HE'S RUNNING AROUND
LOOKING FOR SOME KIND
OF HOT GIRL.
HUH!
WHO ISN'T?
I DON'T THINK WE'VE MET.
I'M... I'M ROSS.
I KNOW.
YOU'RE THE GUY
WHO WOULDN'T CHIP IN
FOR THE HANDYMAN.
NEVER MIND.
NO, I ACTUALLY THOUGHT
IT WAS REALLY UNFAIR
THE WAY EVERYONE
REACTED.
I MEAN, YOU HAD
JUST MOVED IN.
I HAD JUST MOVED IN.
THANK YOU.
LISTEN, UM...
JEN.
JEN, I KNOW THIS
MAY SOUND A LITTLE...
( awkward stammer )
BUT, UH...
WOULD YOU MAYBE
WANT TO GRAB A CUP
OF COFFEE SOMETIME, OR...?
SURE.
THAT WOULD BE NICE.
UM...
OH.
MY NUMBER'S ON THERE.
GIVE ME A CALL.
I WILL GIVE YOU A CALL.
I'LL SEE YOU LATER.
OKAY.
FORGOT MY PAPER.
THAT WAS AMAZING.
OH, PHOEBE AND GARY
ARE SO GOING
TO HEAR ABOUT
THIS AT DINNER.
THAT WAS AMAZING.
WE ARE THE HOTTEST.
NO ONE IS HOTTER
THAN WE ARE.
WE'RE THE BEST.
NO, YOU'RE THE BEST.
I AM THE BEST.
HEY, GUYS.
WHAT YOU BEEN DOING?
HEY, JOEY, ISN'T
THAT THE GIRL
WHO WAVED AT YOU THE OTHER DAY?
I DON'T KNOW, BUT I CAN SEE
THROUGH
YOUR SHEET.
YEAH. YEAH,
THAT'S HER.
BUT YOU KNOW WHAT?
IT DOESN'T MATTER.
I'LL NEVER GET
TO MEET HER ANYWAY
BECAUSE IT'S IMPOSSIBLE
TO FIND HER APARTMENT.
SHE LIVES IN, LIKE, SOME
HOT-GIRL PARALLEL UNIVERSE
OR SOMETHING.
WHAT ARE YOU TALKING ABOUT?
SHE OBVIOUSLY LIVES
ON THE SECOND FLOOR
SEVENTH APARTMENT
FROM THE LEFT.
NO, NO, NO.
SHE LIVES ON
THE THIRD FLOOR
EIGHTH APARTMENT
FROM THE LEFT.
NO. THOSE FIRST TWO WINDOWS--
THAT'S THE LOBBY.
AND THAT OTHER WINDOW OVER
THERE-- THAT'S THE STAIRWAY.
YOU'VE BEEN
COUNTING WRONG.
I DID NOT KNOW THAT.
THANK YOU, MONICA.
I CAN'T BELIEVE
I ALMOST LOST ANOTHER GIRL
BECAUSE OF COUNTING.
SO, ARE YOU READY?
YEAH. I'LL
JUST GET MY COAT.
OKAY.
( knocking on door )
COULD YOU GET THAT?
SURE.
( screaming )
NO! NO!
PLEASE, SIT.
FIRST, I WOULD
LIKE TO SAY
THANK YOU FOR AGREEING
TO SEE ME AGAIN.
THAT'S, UH,
QUITE ALL RIGHT.
BUT I FEEL OBLIGATED
TO TELL YOU
THAT THIS MEETING
IS BEING VIDEOTAPED.
OKAY, UM...
WELL, FIRST,
I WOULD LIKE TO START
BY APOLOGIZING FOR KISSING YOU
AND, UH, FOR YELLING AT YOU.
FAIR ENOUGH.
NOW, YOU'RE PROBABLY
GOING TO HIRE
ONE OF THE
PEOPLE WHO, UH...
WHO DID NOT, UM...
YELL AT YOU AND STORM OUT.
MM-HMM.
AND I THINK THAT'S
A BIG MISTAKE AND HERE'S WHY.
I MADE A HUGE FOOL OF MYSELF
AND I CAME BACK.
THAT SHOWS COURAGE.
WHEN I THOUGHT
YOU WANTED SEX
IN EXCHANGE FOR THIS JOB,
I SAID NO.
THAT SHOWS INTEGRITY.
AND I WAS
NOT AFRAID
TO STAND UP FOR MYSELF
AND THAT SHOWS COURAGE.
OKAY, NOW, I KNOW THAT
I'VE ALREADY SAID COURAGE
BUT, YOU KNOW,
YOU GOT TO HAVE COURAGE.
AND, UM...
AND FINALLY, WHEN I THOUGHT
YOU WERE MAKING SEXUAL ADVANCES
IN THE WORKPLACE
I SAID NO
AND I WAS NOT LITIGIOUS.
SO THERE YOU GO.
YOU GOT...
YOU GOT COURAGE
YOU GOT INTEGRITY,
YOU GOT COURAGE AGAIN
AND NOT LITIGIOUS.
LOOK, MISTER...
ZELNER.
ZELNER. I KNEW THAT.
OH, I KNEW THAT.
UH...
I REALLY, REALLY WANT THIS JOB.
AND I THINK...
I THINK I WOULD BE
REALLY GOOD AT IT.
YOU KNOW WHAT?
YEAH?
I MAY REGRET THIS,
BUT, UH...
I'M GOING TO GIVE YOU A SHOT.
OH, YOU ARE?
MM-HMM.
REALLY?
YEAH.
OH, THANK YOU.
OH, GOD...
OH, WOULD IT BE
COMPLETELY INAPPROPRIATE
IF I GAVE YOU A HUG?
YES.
OKAY.
WELL, THEN, HOW ABOUT
A HANDSHAKE?
AH, OH, GOD,
I'M SORRY.
I, UH...
OH, GOD, I'M SORRY.
I DID NOT MEAN
TO TOUCH THAT--
I MEAN YOU.
THERE.
THERE, UM...
OKAY, SO,
THANK YOU.
I'M GOING TO LEAVE.
THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
THANK YOU SO...
HEY, I'LL SEE YOU MONDAY.
OKAY.
ARE YOU TIRED,
CHANDLER?
YOU BETTER BELIEVE
HE'S TIRED
AFTER THE DAY WE HAD
IF YOU KNOW WHAT I MEAN.
YOU KNOW WHAT I MEAN?
HONEY, THE TORTILLA CHIPS
KNOW WHAT YOU MEAN.
SO, CHANDLER, DO YOU LIKE
THAT BADGE I GOT YOU?
OH, YEAH, IT'S SO COOL.
NOW I GOT TO GO.
OFFICER BING'S GOT A 10-100.
THAT'S PEE-PEE.
PHOEBE, YOU...
YOU HAVE A...
A TWIG IN YOUR HAIR.
OH... UM, WE KIND OF
TOOK A LITTLE DETOUR
ON OUR WAY OVER HERE.
YEAH, WE WERE TAKING
A LITTLE STROLL THROUGH THE PARK
AND NO ONE WAS AROUND, SO...
YOU DIDN'T.
WE DID.
WE VIOLATED SECTION 12
PARAGRAPH SEVEN
OF THE CRIMINAL CODE.
THE PARK, HUH?
PUBLIC PLACE.
MM-HMM.
I HEAR YOU.
CAN YOU EXCUSE ME FOR A SECOND?
OH...
HI, CHANDLER.
MONICA, THIS IS
THE MEN'S ROOM.
ISN'T IT?
YES, IT IS.
BUT, SEE, I'VE ALWAYS FOUND
THE MEN'S BATHROOM VERY SEXUAL.
HAVEN'T YOU?
NO.
AND IF I DID, I DON'T THINK
WE'D BE GOING OUT.
MONICA, THIS IS
GETTING RIDICULOUS.
COME ON, WE CAN'T
LET THEM WIN.
WE HAVE ALREADY PROVED
THAT WE ARE HOT, OKAY?
SO WHY ARE YOU GETTING SO
OBSESSED ABOUT THIS THING?
BECAUSE PHOEBE AND GARY
ARE IN THAT...
CAN'T-KEEP-THEIR-
HANDS-OFF-EACH-OTHER
DOING-IT-IN-
THE-PARK PHASE.
OH! SO?
SO... IT'S REALLY SAD
THAT WE'RE NOT
THERE ANYMORE.
OH, WOW, IS THAT WHAT
THIS HAS ALL BEEN ABOUT?
WASN'T IT A LOT
MORE EXCITING
WHEN WE WERE,
YOU KNOW
ALL OVER EACH OTHER
ALL THE TIME?
WELL, YEAH,
THAT WAS GREAT.
THAT WAS REALLY... GREAT.
BUT TO TELL YOU THE TRUTH
I'M MORE EXCITED ABOUT
WHERE WE ARE NOW.
REALLY?
YEAH.
I'VE NEVER BEEN
IN A RELATIONSHIP
THAT'S LASTED THIS
LONG BEFORE, YOU KNOW?
AND TO GET PAST
THE BEGINNING
AND STILL WANT TO BE AROUND
EACH OTHER ALL THE TIME--
WELL, I THINK THAT'S
PRETTY INCREDIBLE.
AND THE FACT THAT THIS
IS ALL HAPPENING WITH YOU...
YEAH, I THINK THAT'S
PRETTY EXCITING.
THAT'S SO SWEET.
I KNOW THAT I WAS ACTING
A LITTLE CRAZY, BUT, UM...
I FEEL THE SAME WAY.
YEAH?
YOU KNOW WHAT
I JUST REALIZED?
YOU JUST FREAKED OUT
ABOUT OUR RELATIONSHIP.
I DID NOT.
YES, YOU DID;
ADMIT IT.
YOU FREAKED OUT.
OKAY, I FREAKED OUT A LITTLE.
A LITTLE? YOU FREAKED
OUT BIG TIME, OKAY?
AND I FIXED IT.
WE HAVE SWITCHED PLACES.
I AM THE RELATIONSHIP KING
AND YOU ARE THE CRAZY,
IRRATIONAL SCREW-UP.
OOH-OOH!
AND NOW WE'RE BACK.
I CANNOT BELIEVE
ROSS IS BUYING THIS.
THANK GOD.
I CAN'T
WATCH HIM ANYMORE.
YOU GUYS READY FOR THE MOVIES?
YEAH.
THANK YOU FOR LOANING US
PAMELA AND YASMINE.
MAN, THEY CANNOT GET ENOUGH.
[Captioned by
The Caption Center
WGBH Educational Foundation]